Hilokal Privacy Policy
======================

Privacy Policy Summary
----------------------

Hereʼs Hilokalʼs privacy Policy. Have a read through and understand how we respect your privacy and your data. First, hereʼs the short version in bullet points:

* **Data Collection**: We only collect personal data necessary for providing our services, such as your contact details, profile information, and activity data. We collect audio recordings only when you request us to, and 2 minutes of audio when a user-report is triggered.
* **Usage and Storage**: Your data is used to create your profile, enhance community safety, and improve our services. We store your data securely and retain it only as long as necessary.
* **Third-Party Sharing**: We share your data with third parties only with your explicit consent or to comply with legal obligations. This includes services for analytics, hosting, and payment processing.
* **Your Rights**: You have the right to access, correct, delete, and restrict the processing of your data. You can also revoke your consent at any time and lodge complaints with the relevant authorities.

Full Privacy Policy
-------------------

Below you will find how Hilokal handles your personal data in our mobile app and website. Your data protection is important to us.

### Contact

Hilokal Co LTD.  
CEO: JeongHo YUN [admin@hilokal.com](https://www.hilokal.com/en/app/admin@hilokal.com)  
Address: #407\_c, 37, Seongsui-ro 22-gil, Seongdong-gu, Seoul  
주소 : 서울시 성동구 성수이로 22길 37 407\_c호

Data Protection Officer  
Asong Choi  
Address: #407\_c, 37, Seongsui-ro 22-gil, Seongdong-gu, Seoul  
주소 : 서울시 성동구 성수이로 22길 37 407\_c호

### 1\. Personal Data

Personal data includes any information that can identify an individual. The categories of personal data we process are:

* **Contact Details**: This includes your email address, and location. (not shared with other Hilokal members)
* **Profile Information**: This covers details such as your age, gender, and city.
* **Profile Images**: Any personal images you upload to your profile.
* **Message Content**: This includes images, voice messages, corrections, and topics shared within your messages.
* **Communications with Hilokal**: Any correspondence you have with us.
* **Log Files**: Information about your visits to our website and apps.
* **Online Identifiers**: This includes cookie IDs, IP addresses, and advertising IDs.
* **Activity Data**: Records of your interactions with our apps and websites, such as clicks, screens viewed, and pages visited.
* **Audio recordings**: Hilokal audio is temporarily recorded for purposes described below, but is immediately deleted after 2 minutes unless:
    * For user-reports review: if one or more reported user is a participant of a conversation room, the last 2 minutes of audio in such conversation room is saved for user-report review and community moderation to protect other users.
    * When you request recording: The word-count feature records and stores your audio if you request.
    * When a Premium Host makes a recording Premium Hosts have the ability to record conversation taking place in the rooms. All users are notified the audio room is being recorded. You may only speak and have your voice recorded if you explicitly consent while in the conversation room.

### 2\. Purposes of Use

We collect personal data only to the extent and for the purposes you provide it to us, such as when registering an account. We use and store your personal data as part of our services for the following purposes:

* **User Profile Creation**: To create a public user profile for you on Hilokal.
* **Service Communications**: To send you relevant service information via email or push notifications, such as updates on your membership status, missed calls/messages, and new followers.
* **Targeted Advertising**: To display targeted ads in the app.
* **Partner Matching**: To help you find Hilokal partners nearby.
* **Service Optimization**: To understand how Hilokal is used and to optimize our service.
* **Curated Language Learning Community**: To ensure a secure, member-only environment for language learners. We prevent abuse and promptly ban offenders by verifying profile picture authenticity and comparing hashed photos with known scam images.
* **Community Safety**: To maintain a safe, friendly, and accountable environment in one-on-one chats, parties, clubs, and group chats by encouraging authentic communication.
* **Correspondence**: To communicate with you.
* **Survey Participation**: To facilitate your participation in our surveys.
* **Contract Processing**: To process any contracts with you (purchasing subscriptions, in-app purchases)
* **Advertising and Newsletters**: To send advertising materials such as newsletters.
* **Quality Assurance and Statistics**: To ensure quality and collect statistical data.
* **Member Profile Discovery**: To create a profile that helps others find and connect with you.

Only verified members can contact you, and we never display your email, exact location, or any information you choose not to share. We do not share your personal data with third parties unless you give explicit consent or we are legally obligated to do so, such as by a court order. To provide functionality and for usage analysis and marketing purposes, we collect relevant information.

### 3\. Legal Basis

We process your data according to the following legal grounds:

* **Consent**: As per Art. 6(1)(a) of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), when you have given consent for cookies or advertising.
* **Contract Fulfillment**: Under Art. 6(1)(b) GDPR, to establish and execute the contract, such as when you join our community.
* **Compliance with Legal Obligations**: According to Art. 6(1)(c) GDPR, to meet legal requirements.
* **Legitimate Interests**: Based on Art. 6(1)(f) GDPR, for processing messages you share with your Hilokal partners in one-on-one chats, conversation rooms, and group chats, aligning with our legitimate interests. Furthermore, statistical data and online identifiers are processed under our legitimate interests, in accordance with Art. 6(1)(f) GDPR.

#### Legitimate Interests

When processing your data, we aim to achieve the following legitimate interests:

* **Community Integrity and Credibility**: To uphold and enhance the integrity and credibility of our community.
* **Misuse Prevention**: To protect against misuse and fraudulent activities.
* **Service Provision and Improvement**: To deliver and enhance our services.
* **Statistics and Analytics**: To gather statistical data and analyze service usage.

### 4\. Sources of Data

Unless stated otherwise, we collect data directly from you, including from the devices you use.

### 5\. Data Retention Policy

We retain your data under specific conditions to ensure compliance and functionality:

* **Consent-Based Retention**: If you have given consent for specific processing, we retain your data until you withdraw your consent (e.g., by deleting your account).
* **Contractual Requirements**: If data is needed to fulfill an agreement, we retain it until the contractual relationship ends or legal retention periods expire.
* **Legitimate Interest**: If data is used based on legitimate interests, we retain it until your overriding interests requiring deletion or anonymization.
* **Account Deletion**: When you delete your account, your personal information will be permanently removed within 30 days, but we keep your associated email address and Hilokal ID to process future deletion requests and respond to user inquiries. Additionally, any messages you have sent to a Hilokal partner will remain; however, the sender will be anonymized.
* **Membership Applications**: We store membership applications, including personal information, from the tutors. This information will be deleted within 30 days of account deletion.
* **Rule Violation Consequences**: To maintain a safe environment, we take violations of Terms of Service or Community Guidelines seriously. We may retain anonymous personal identifiers for up to 24 months to prevent access to the Hilokal service during that period.

### 6\. Children’s Information Policy

Children and individuals under the age of 16 are not permitted to use Hilokal. If you are a parent and discover that your child is using Hilokal without your permission, please contact us at [admin@hilokal.com](https://www.hilokal.com/en/app/admin@hilokal.com).

### 7\. Cookies

Cookies and similar technologies are small text files or pieces of code that often contain a unique identification code. When you visit a website or use a mobile application, your device is asked for permission to save this file and access certain information. Information collected through cookies may include the date and time of your visit and how you use the website or app. We use cookies to:

* **Remember Information**: So that you don’t have to re-enter it during your visit or on subsequent visits.
* **Provide Personalized Content**: To offer custom and personalized content and information.
* **Monitor Service Effectiveness**: To assess and ensure the effectiveness of our services.
* **Aggregate Metrics**: To gather and analyze data such as total visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns.
* **Diagnose Issues**: To identify and fix technology problems.
* **Streamline Access**: To help you efficiently access your information after signing in.
* **Maintain Login**: To keep you logged in during your session.
* **Ensure Community Safety**: To keep the Hilokal community safe for all members.

### 8\. Data Recipients

We use your personal information within our company and share it only with third-party companies involved in fulfilling the contracts or providing relevant services. We forward the following customer data to third parties:

* **Service Analysis**: To analyze how Hilokal is used and to optimize our service and design, we share pseudonymous usage and personal data with Google Analytics, Firebase Analytics, and UX Cam.
* **Personalized Advertising**: With your explicit consent, to make ads more personal, we may share anonymized personal information, such as age, gender, and device identifiers with Admob by Google, and Facebook Audience Network. Both iOS and Android devices have resettable advertising identifiers that companies can use to target ads based on the apps you use.
* **Community Moderation**: To enforce our community moderation policies, we share personal data with Camino Moderation services to process user reports.
* **Disabling Mobile Advertising Identifiers**:  
    iOS Devices: Go to your iOS device settings and enable the “Limit ad trackingˮ option.  
    Android Devices: Go to your Android device settings and enable the “Opt out of ads personalizationˮ option.

#### 8.1 Registration and Authentication

By registering or authenticating, users allow Hilokal to identify them securely and give them access to its services. Depending on what is described below, third parties may provide registration and authentication services. In this case, Hilokal will be able to access some data stored by these third-party services for registration or identification purposes, with the userʼs explicit consent:

* **Facebook Authentication (Meta, Inc.)**: Facebook Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Facebook, Inc. and is connected to the Facebook social network. The personal data collected includes various types of data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/).
* **Firebase Authentication (Google Inc.)**: Firebase Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Google Inc. To simplify the registration and authentication process, Firebase Authentication can make use of third-party identity providers and save the information on its platform. Personal data collected: email. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
* **Google OAuth (Google Inc.)**: Google OAuth is a registration and authentication service provided by Google Inc. and is connected to the Google network. The personal data collected includes various types of data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
* **Kakao Authentication**: Kakao Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Kakao Corp. The personal data collected includes various types of data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: South Korea – [Privacy Policy](https://www.kakao.com/policy/privacy).
* **Naver Authentication**: Naver Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Naver Corp. The personal data collected includes various types of data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: South Korea – [Privacy Policy](https://policy.naver.com/policy/privacy_en.html).
* **Sign in with Apple (Apple Inc.)**: Sign in with Apple is a registration and authentication service provided by Apple Inc. In cases where users are required to provide their email address, Sign in with Apple may generate a private relay address on behalf of users that automatically forwards messages to their verified personal email account, thereby shielding their actual email address from the owner. Personal data processed: email address, first name, last name, user ID. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/).

#### 8.2 Hosting and Backend Infrastructure

These services are used for hosting data and files that enable Hilokal to operate and be distributed, as well as providing the infrastructure needed to run specific features or parts of Hilokal. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the exact location where personal data is stored.

* **Amazon Web Services (AWS) (Amazon Web Services, Inc.)**: AWS is a hosting and backend service provided by Amazon.com Inc. A wide range of personal data, including sign-in data, images, and message content, is stored on AWS infrastructure as Hilokalʼs main hosting and infrastructure provider. Places of processing: Germany and the United States – [Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/).
* **Google Cloud Platform (Google Inc.)**: Google Cloud Platform is a hosting and backend service provided by Google Inc. Personal data collected includes various types of data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://cloud.google.com/terms/data-processing-terms).
* **Vultr (The Constant Company, LLC)**: Vultr is hosting and backend service provided by The Constant Company, LLC. All real-time audio communication is forwarded, but not stored, by servers on the Vultr network. Place of processing: Singapore, India – [Privacy Policy](https://www.vultr.com/legal/privacy/).

#### 8.3 Payment Handling

Payment handling services allow Hilokal to process transactions securely. For enhanced security, Hilokal does not process or store credit card details, only using the necessary information to complete transactions with the financial intermediaries involved. Some of these services may also send you timed messages, such as emails with invoices or payment notifications.

* **Apple App Store Payments (Apple Inc.)**: Hilokal uses a payment service provided by Apple Inc. for in-app purchases. Personal data required to complete purchases is processed by Apple as described in their [privacy policy for the App Store](https://policy.naver.com/policy/privacy_en.html). Personal data processed: payment information. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy.](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/)
* **Google Play Store Payments (Google Ireland Limited)**: Hilokal uses a payment service provided by Google Ireland Limited for in-app purchases. Personal data required to complete purchases is processed by Google as described in their [privacy policy for the Google Play](https://policies.google.com/privacy) Store. Personal data processed: payment information. Place of processing: Ireland – [Privacy Policy.](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

#### 8.4 Service Monitoring

These services allow Hilokal to monitor the usage and behavior of its components to improve features, performance, operation, maintenance, and troubleshooting. The personal data processed depends on the service’s characteristics and implementation.

* Crashlytics (Google Inc.): Crashlytics, provided by Google Inc., helps improve app stability and reduce crashes. Personal data collected: geographic location, unique device identifiers (e.g., Google Advertiser ID or IDFA), and various data as specified in the service’s privacy policy. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy.](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
* Sentry (Functional Software, Inc.): Sentry is a monitoring service that helps improve application stability and performance. Personal data collected: device information, error details, and various types of data as specified in the service’s privacy policy. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy.](https://sentry.io/privacy/)

#### 8.5 Contact Management and Messaging

These services enable communication with users outside the app, such as via push notifications and email. They may manage a database of email contacts, phone contacts, or other contact information to communicate with users. These services may also collect data about when the message was viewed and interacted with, such as clicking on links included in the message.

* **Firebase Cloud Messaging (Google Inc.)**: Firebase Cloud Messaging, provided by Google Inc., allows sending messages and notifications to users across platforms like Android, iOS, and the web. Messages can be sent to single devices, groups of devices, or specific topics or user segments. Personal data collected: various types of data as specified in the service’s privacy policy. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/).
* **AWS Pinpoint (Amazon Web Services, Inc.)**: AWS Pinpoint, provided by Amazon Web Services, Inc., is a service that enables sending targeted push notifications and emails to users. It also allows for tracking message delivery and user interactions. Personal data collected: various types of data as specified in the service’s privacy policy. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/).

#### 8.6 Traffic and Usage Analytics

These services enable us to monitor and analyze web and mobile traffic, tracking how users interact with Hilokal.

* **Internal Analytics (Hilokal)**: We use an internal analytics system that does not involve third parties. Personal data collected: cookies and usage data.
* **Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**: This web analysis service tracks and examines the use of Hilokal, prepares reports, and shares them with other Google services. Google may also use the data to contextualize and personalize its ads. Personal data collected: cookies and usage data. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).
* **Firebase Analytics (Google Inc.)**: This service tracks usage data and shares information with other Firebase tools, such as Crash Reporting, Authentication, Remote Config, or Notifications. Users can opt out of certain features through device settings. Personal data collected: cookies, unique device identifiers for advertising (e.g., Google Advertiser ID or IDFA), and usage data. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/).
* **Facebook Ads Conversion Tracking (Facebook, Inc.)**: This service connects data from Facebook ads with actions performed on Hilokal. Personal data collected: cookies and usage data. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).
* **TestFlight (Apple Inc.)**: This analytics service provided by Apple tracks app usage and performance. Personal data collected: cookies, email address, and usage data. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/itunes/testflight/sren/terms.html).

For further details on how these services use your data, please refer to their respective privacy policies.

#### 8.7 Advertising

Ads help us fund Hilokal and keep most features free. We share your age, gender, location, and device information with advertisers to make ads more relevant and increase our revenue. We only share your data with your consent, which you can revoke at any time. Below are the advertising services we use:

* **AdMob (Google Inc.)**: AdMob displays ads based on cookies, unique device identifiers (e.g., Google Advertiser ID or IDFA), and usage data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out.
* **Facebook Audience Network (Facebook, Inc.)**: This service uses cookies and device identifiers to show ads based on user preferences. Users can manage ad preferences in the Facebook ad settings. Personal data collected: cookies, unique device identifiers, and usage data. Place of processing: United States [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen).

For more details on these services and how to opt out, refer to their respective privacy policies.

#### 8.8 A/B Testing and Content Performance

These services allow Hilokal to track and analyze user responses to changes in web traffic or behavior regarding changes to the structure, text, or any other component of Hilokal.

* **Firebase Remote Config (Google Inc.)**: An A/B testing and configuration service. Personal data collected: various types as specified in the privacy policy. Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/).
* **Google Optimize (Google Inc.)**: A tool for A/B testing, website testing, and personalization. Personal data collected: various types as specified in the privacy policy. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

### 9\. Data Transfer to Third Countries

Data collected within the region of your residence, which may be European Economic Area (EEA), is transferred to countries outside the EEA, including the United States, Singapore, India, and South Korea. We ensure that appropriate safeguards are in place to protect your personal data in accordance with GDPR.

These safeguards include:

* **Adequacy Decisions**: Transfers to countries that the European Commission has deemed to provide an adequate level of data protection.
* **Standard Contractual Clauses**: Use of standard data protection clauses approved by the European Commission.
* **Other Legal Mechanisms**: Use of other legally recognized mechanisms and safeguards as required.

### 10\. Your Rights

As a Hilokal user, you have the following rights regarding your personal data:

* **Access and Information**: Request details on whether and what personal data is processed by us, and how it has been processed.
* **Correction**: Request amendments to your personal data.
* **Deletion**: Request deletion of your personal data, for example by using the “Delete Accountˮ option in “My Page-Settings-Manage accountˮ. However, deletion may be refused in accordance with GDPR and other applicable laws.
* **Restriction**: Request restrictions on the processing of your personal data under certain conditions. When this right is exercised, the data may be stored but can only be processed for limited purposes, and it cannot be used for other purposes without the your consent.
* **Object**: Request objections to the processing of your personal data under certain conditions. Revocation of Consent: Revoke your consent to data processing at any time, with future effect.
* **Data Portability**: Receive your personal data in a common, structured, and machine-readable format via the “Manage accountˮ ⇒ “Download personal dataˮ ⇒ “Submit Request” button in “My Pageˮ. Your Data will be sent to you via Direct Message in Hilokal as a ZIP file.
* **Contact**: For questions, comments, complaints, or requests related to data protection. [admin@hilokal.com](https://www.hilokal.com/en/app/admin@hilokal.com)
* **Complaints**: Lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority if you believe your personal data processing violates legal regulations.

### 11\. Automated Decision-Making and Profiling

We may use automated decision-making processes, including profiling, to provide personalized services or ads. This means decisions are made by algorithms without human intervention. Profiling helps us analyze or predict your personal preferences, interests, behavior, and other attributes. You have the right not to be subject to decisions based solely on automated processing that significantly affect you. This right does not apply if the decision is necessary for a contract, authorized by law, or based on your explicit consent.

### 12\. Data Provision Requirements

Unless explicitly stated otherwise, providing data is not mandatory or required when it is collected. However, please note that restriction or objection to the processing of your personal data may result in restriction of certain services requiring the data.

### Date of issue of this data privacy statement

2024-06-11
